logz.io 2019-11-01

# Privacy Policy

Last revised on October 27, 2019

We, at LogsHero Ltd. (“we” or the “Company”), are committed to protect the privacy of:

  1. individuals who visit or access our website at logz.io (the “ **Website** ”);
  2. our customers and business partners (“ **Customer(s)** ”), who are licensed to access or use our log management and analysis platform (the “ **Logz.io Platform** ”) and any other services offered by the Company (collectively with the Logz.io Platform and Website: the “ **Services** ”). Please note that although we do not intend that our Customers will share Personal Information with us, if we do process Personal Information on behalf of our Customers, we will process it in accordance with the provisions of this policy, as applicable;
  3. any individual who is authorized by our Customers to use the Services or has access to any of the data managed and analyzed by the Company (“ **User(s)** ”).

Please note that the term “ ** _you_** ” shall refer to website’s visitors, Customers and Users, as applicable.

Our privacy policy (“ **Privacy Policy** ”) will help you understand what types of information we collect through the Services, how the Company uses it, and what choices you have. We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully and use it to make informed decisions. By using our Services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and your continued use of the Services constitutes your ongoing agreement to it.

In this Privacy Policy you will read about:

  *  **What types of information we collect?**
  *  ** **Cookies****
  *  ** **How we use the information we collect?****
  *  ** **With whom do we share the information that we collect?****
  *  ** **International Transfer****
  *  ** **Your privacy rights****
  *  ** **For how long do we retain the information that we collect?****
  *  ** **How do we safeguard your information?****
  *  ** **Advertisements****
  *  ** **Marketing****
  *  ** **Minors****
  *  ** **Updates or amendments to the Privacy Policy****
  *  ** **How to contact us****

We may collect the following types of information from or about you:

  * ##  **Personal Information**

Personal Information is individually identifiable information, namely information that identifies an individual or may with reasonable effort to identify an individual. We gather the following types of Personal Information:

  *  **Registration details** : When ordering or registering to our Services, we may collect certain information that can be used to identify you (as the Customer’s point of contact or as a User) such as: name, email address, postal address, phone number, user IDs and other relevant details which are relevant to the Customer. We may also use our trusted third parties to enrich the information associated with you.
  *  **Customer’s payment information** : In order for you to enjoy all of the functions which we offer, we collect payment information from you, including your credit card number and bank account details. Please note that your billing information, to the extent provided by you, is forwarded directly to a third party billing or clearing company engaged by us and is not kept by us.
  *  **Voluntary information** : We also collect information which you provide us voluntarily. For example, when you respond to communications from us, ask our support, and communicate with us in any means, including, without limitation, via email, phone, Website, Logz.io Platform or otherwise, or when you share additional information about yourself through your use of the Services, then all such communications may be recorded.
  *  **Device information** : We also collect specific types of connection details and information with regard to your device, software or hardware that may identify you, such as: online identifiers, device’s unique identifiers (e.g. UDID, MAC address), IP address and geolocation.
  *  **Forum Information:** As part of the Services, Users may communicate with other Users through the Website and upload content to our forums (“ **Forum Information** ”). Such Forum Information may consist of, for example, Users’ comments and tips for utilizing the Services, feedbacks, etc. We and other Users will be exposed to your username and any additional information you upload to the forum, including Personal Information. We recommend that you secure your anonymity and information so that you do not allow others to identify you. By uploading Forum Information, you represent that you have all the necessary consents and permissions from each identifiable individual referenced in your content to use their Personal Information as part of our Services.

  * ##  **Non-personal Information**

Non-personal Information is non-identifiable information that, when taken alone, cannot be used to identify you. As such, we are not aware of the identity of the user from which the Non-personal Information was collected.

  *  **Analytics Data** : Our servers automatically record certain information regarding the use of our Services. Such data may include information such as the website that a User was visiting before accessing our Services and other statistics related to our Services. We also perform statistical analysis on all of the data and metadata which is collected through our Services.

We use this information to administer the Services and analyze this information to improve and enhance the Services by expanding their features and functionality. Such data is also used for troubleshooting errors and bugs as well as for research and analytics purposes about your use of the Services.  
For the avoidance of doubt, if we combine Personal Information with Non-personal Information (e.g. analytics data), the combined information will be treated as Personal Information as long as it remains combined.

  *  **Anonymous information** : We may anonymize or de-identify the information collected by the Services or via other means so that the information cannot, on its own, personally identify you. Our use and disclosure of such aggregated or de-identified information are not subject to any restrictions under this Privacy Policy, and we may disclose it to others without limitation and for any purpose.
  * ##  **End-User Data**

By using the Logz.io Platform, we manage and analyze Customer’s logs and other data that are transmitted through our Customers’ platforms. This data may include records of operations of Customer’s applications and systems and other information relating to Customer’s employees’/ end-users’ activities (“ **End-User Data** “). It may also include data, logs, text, audio, video or images that a Customer or any User uses in connection with Customer’s account and any computational results that a Customer or any User derives from the foregoing through their use of the Product.

Such End-User Data is provided by the Customer (or its Users) and processed by us on our cloud computing servers. The Company provides such services as a “data processor”, acting under the sole direction of its Customers and Users.

Please note that End-User Data is exclusively controlled by the Customer, meaning that the Customer (or any Users authorized by the Customer to use the Logz.io Platform on its behalf), maintain ownership of their related End-User Data and determine their own policies regarding the content that is provided within the End-User Data, the access permissions and the retention of the End-User Data.

Here are some examples of End-User Data that may be recorded and processed when you use the Logz.io Platform (keep in mind that they are only examples and there may be others):

  * Digital files created or transmitted through User’s platforms, such as text files;
  * Contact directories (such as names and email addresses);
  * Device identifiers – such as the Internet Protocol (IP) address and other types of unique device identifiers relating to Customer’s and its users’ devices.
  * Non-personal Information (as defined below), including usernames, directory names, server names, share names, file names, configurations, logs related to the Company (e.g. event logs), browsing events and technical information provided by the Customer’s and its Users’ devices, etc.

Please note that such End-User Data may include Personal Information. If you (as a Customer or a User) provide to us or to third-parties acting on our behalf any Personal Information relating to other individuals (e.g. employees, end-users, etc.) in connection with your use of the Logz.io Platform, you represent that you have the authority to do so and to permit us to use the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

For the removal of doubt, please note that with respect to login information that is provided by the Customer(s) or its User(s), the Company will act as a “data controller” and will handle such information in accordance with the provisions of this Privacy Policy.

If you have any reason to believe that our Services are misused, in any way, please do not hesitate to inform us at: [privacy@logz.io](mailto:privacy@logz.io)

When you visit or access our websites, or when you interact or engage with our Services, we use (and authorize third parties to use) web beacons, cookies, pixel tags, scripts, tags, API and other technologies (“ **Tracking Technologies** ”).

The Tracking Technologies allow us to automatically collect information about you and your online behavior, as well as your device (for example your computer or mobile device), in order to enhance your navigation on our Services, improve our Services’ performance and customize your experience on our Services. We also use this information to collect statistics about the usage of our Services, perform analytics, deliver content which is tailored to your interests and administer services to our Users, advertisers, publishers, customers and partners.

We also allow third parties to collect information about you through Tracking Technologies for the same purposes mentioned above.

 **What are cookies?**

Cookies are small text files (composed only of letters and numbers) that a web server places on your computer or mobile device when you visit a webpage. When used, the cookie can help make our Services more user-friendly, for example by remembering your language preferences and settings. You can find more information about cookies at <https://www.allaboutcookies.org/>.

Cookies are widely used in order to make websites work in an efficient way. The use of cookies allows you to navigate between pages efficiently. Cookies remember your preferences and make the interaction between you and the Services smoother and more efficient. Cookies are also used to help ensure that the advertisements you see online are relevant to you and your interests.

##  **Storing Tracking Technologies**

We store Tracking Technologies when you visit or access our Services (for example, when you are visiting our Websites) – these are called “First Party Tracking Technologies”. In addition, Tracking Technologies are stored by other third parties (for example our analytics service providers, business partners and advertisers) – these are called “Third Party Tracking Technologies”.

Both types of Tracking Technologies may be stored either for the duration of your visit on our Services or for repeat visits.

###  **What types of Tracking Technologies do we use?**

There are five main types of Tracking Technologies:

  *  **Strictly necessary Tracking Technologies** –

These Tracking Technologies are essential to enable you to login, navigate around and use the features of our Services, or to provide a service requested by you (such as your username). We do not need to obtain your consent in order to use these Tracking Technologies. These Tracking Technologies can be used for security and integrity reasons – for example, to detect violation of our policies and for support or security features.

  *  **Functionality Tracking Technologies –**

These Tracking Technologies allow our Services to remember choices you make (such as your language) and provide enhanced and personalized features. For example, these Tracking Technologies are used for authentication (to remember when you are logged in) and support other features of our Services.

  *  **Performance Tracking Technologies** **–**

These Tracking Technologies collect information about your online activity (for example the duration of your visit on our Services), including behavioral data and content engagement metrics. These Tracking Technologies are used for analytics, research and to perform statistics (based on aggregated information).

  *  **Marketing or Advertising Tracking Technologies** **–**

These Tracking Technologies are used to deliver tailored offers and advertisements to you, based on your derived interests, as well as to perform email marketing campaigns. They can also be used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. They are usually placed by our advertisers (for example advertising networks) and provide them insights about the people who see and interact with their ads, visit their websites or use their app.

  *  **Social media Tracking Technologies** **–  **

Our website includes social media features, such as the Facebook “Like” or “Share” buttons. These features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Services. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy statement of the company providing these features.

 **Tracking Technologies**|  **Type**|  **Purpose**  
---|---|---  
Google  
Hotjar| Third-party Tracking Technology|  **Performance Tracking Technologies:**

These Tracking Technologies are used to collect information regarding how you interact with the content on our Services, attribution purposes (for example, the referral URL), etc. We use the information to compile reports, calculate the revenues due to us and, help us improve the Services and to offer personalized products and content.  
  
Google  
Twitter  
Facebook  
Bing  
Marketo  
Linkedin  
Metadata  
EverString  
Trendemon| Third-party Tracking Technology|  **Marketing or Advertising Tracking Technologies:  
**  
These Tracking Technologies are used to deliver tailored offers and advertisements to you, based on your derived interests, as well as to perform email marketing campaigns. They can also be used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement, as well as help, measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign  
 **Intercom  
Disqus**| Third-party Tracking Technology|  **Functionality Tracking Technologies:**

This Tracking Technology allows our Services to remember choices you make (such as your language) and provide enhanced and personalized features. For example, these Tracking Technologies are used for authentication (to remember when you are logged in) and support other features of our Services.  
  
 **Other cookies**|  First and Third party Tracking Technology|  **Strictly necessary Tracking Technologies:**  
These unlisted cookies might be in use on internal sections of the Services, in order to customize and simplify the user experience on the site by remembering choices you made and your log in credentials.  
  
##  **How to manage your cookie settings**

Please note that we do not recognize or respond to automated browser signals regarding Tracking Technologies, including “Do Not Track” requests. However, there are various ways in which you can manage and control your cookie settings. Please remember that, by deleting or blocking cookies, some of the features of the Services may not work properly or as effectively.

  *  **Turning off cookies via your web browser**

Most web browsers will provide you with some general information about cookies, enable you to see what cookies are stored on your device, allow you to delete them all or on an individual basis, and enable you to block or allow cookies for all websites or individually selected websites. You can also normally turn off third-party cookies separately. Please note that the settings offered by a browser or device often only apply to that particular browser or device. Information about cookies is usually found in the “Help” section of the web browser. Below are some links to some commonly used web browsers:

  * Information about cookies is usually found in the “Help” section of the web browser. Below are some links to some commonly used web browsers:
    *  _[Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en)_
    *  _[Chrome for mobile](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/2392971?hl=en)_
    *  _[Internet Explorer and Microsoft Edge](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies)_
    *  _[Mozilla Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/cookies-information-websites-store-on-your-computer)_
    *  _[Safari](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH19214?locale=en_US)_
  *  **Turning off third-party cookies**  
You can turn off certain third party targeting/advertising cookies by visiting the following link:  _[Network Advertising Initiative](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1)_.

In addition to the purposes listed herein, the information we collect, which may include your Personal Information, is used for the following purposes:

  * To **set up Customers’ accounts** and process their related billing information;

  * To identify and **authenticate Users’ access** to our Services;
  * To **provide Services** to our Customers (or Users) in connection with their respective End-User Data, including:
    * providing tools to search and analyze End-User Data (e.g. for purposes of system troubleshooting, monitoring, forensics, etc.);
    * tagging End-User Data in order to identify specific Users’ activities;
    * indexing User Data into a dedicated data-store; and
    * allowing Customer to perform activities concerning such data (e.g. create searches, visualizations, dashboards and alerts).

  * To **support and troubleshoot** our Services and to respond to queries;
  * To **obtain Users’ feedback** with regards to the Services and to analyze and share Forum Information;
  * To serve you advertisements that are relevant to you and your interests when you use our site (see more under “ **Advertisement** “)

  * To improve and **customize our Services** to Customer’s needs and interests;
  * To **empower our learning system** , which performs statistical analysis on all of the data and metadata which is collected through our Services;
  * To **communicate with you** and to keep you informed of our latest updates and newsletters;
  * To identify and **publicize you as a Customer** on the Website, our client lists, press releases or other marketing documents;
  * To **investigate violations and enforce our policies** , and as required by law, regulation or other governmental authority, or to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process or respond to a government request.

We do not rent or sell any Personal Information. We may disclose Personal Information to other trusted third party service providers or partners for the following purposes:

  * Assisting us with our business operations (e.g. processing and analyzing End-User Data);
  * Storage (e.g. cloud computing service providers);
  * Research and analytics that will enable us to improve the Logz.io Platform and Services;
  * If we have a good faith belief that disclosure of such information is helpful or reasonably necessary to: (i) comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request; (ii) enforce our policies (including our agreements), including investigations of potential violations thereof; (iii) investigate, detect, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities or other wrongdoing, suspected fraud or security issues; (iv) establish or exercise our rights to defend against legal claims; (v) prevent harm to the rights, property or safety of us, our users, yourself or any third party; or (vi) for the purpose of collaborating with law enforcement agencies or in case we find it necessary in order to enforce intellectual property or other legal rights.

In addition, we may transfer or disclose Personal Information to our subsidiaries and other affiliated companies.

Since we operate globally, it may be necessary to transfer data, including Personal Information, to countries outside the European Union. In these instances, we will transfer your data only to such countries as approved by the European Commission as providing an adequate level of data protection or enter into legal agreements ensuring an adequate level of data protection.

You may contact us at any time and request:

  * To access, delete, change or update any Personal Information relating to you (for example, if you believe that your Personal Information is incorrect, you may ask to have it corrected or deleted);
  * That we will cease or limit any further use of your Personal Information (for example, you may ask that we will stop using or sharing your Personal Information with third parties);
  * You also have the right to lodge a complaint with supervisory authority.

Please note that these rights are not absolute and may be subject to our own legitimate interests and regulatory requirements.

If you wish to raise a complaint on how we have handled your Personal Information, you can contact our Data Protection Officer who will investigate the matter. Our Data Protection Officer can be contacted at [privacy@logz.io](mailto:privacy@logz.io).

If you are not satisfied with our response or believe we are collecting or processing your Personal Information not in accordance with the laws, you can file a complaint to the applicable data protection authority.

We retain the information that we collect from Customers and Users for as long as needed to provide our Services and to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements (unless we are instructed otherwise). Retention periods will be determined to take into account the type of information that is collected and the purpose for which it is collected, bearing in mind the requirements applicable to the situation and the need to destroy outdated, unused information at the earliest reasonable time. Under applicable regulations, we will keep records containing Customers Personal Information, account opening documents, communications and anything else as required by applicable laws and regulations.

We may rectify, replenish or remove incomplete or inaccurate information, at any time and at our own discretion.

Please note that End-User Data obtained through our Services is fully controlled by the Customer. This means that the Customer (and not the Company) determines the policies and retention periods of the End-User Data.

We take great care in implementing and maintaining the security of the Logz.io Platform, your information and End-User Data. We employ industry standard procedures to ensure the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of our Customers’ systems and End-User Data, the safety of your Personal Information and prevent unauthorized use of any such information.

However, we cannot guarantee that hackers or unauthorized personnel will not gain access to information despite our efforts. You should note that by using our Services, your information will be transferred through third party infrastructures which are not under our control. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information and End-User Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you feel that your privacy was treated not in accordance with this Privacy Policy, please contact us directly at  [privacy@logz.io](mailto:privacy@logz.io).

We may use a third-party advertising technology to serve advertisements when you access the Site. This technology uses your information with regards to your use of the Services to serve advertisements to you (e.g., by placing third-party cookies on your web browser).

You may opt-out of many third-party ad networks, including those operated by members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) and the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”). For more information about this practice by NAI and DAA members, and your choices regarding having this information used by these companies, including how to opt-out of third-party ad networks operated by NAI and DAA members, please visit their respective websites: <http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!%2F> and [http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN#!/](http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN#!/).

We may use your Personal Information, such as your full name, email address, etc. ourselves or by using our third-party partners for the purpose of providing you with promotional materials, concerning our Services.  
Out of respect to your right to privacy, we provide you within such marketing materials with means to decline receiving further marketing offers from us. In addition, at any time, you may request to unsubscribe and discontinue receiving marketing offers by sending us a blank message with the word “remove” to [privacy@logz.io](mailto:privacy@logz.io).

Please note that even if you unsubscribe from our marketing mailing list, we may continue to send you service-related updates and notifications.

##  **Corporate transaction**

We may share information, including Personal Information, in the event of a corporate transaction (e.g. sale of a substantial part of our business, merger, consolidation or asset sale of an asset or transfer in the operation thereof) of the Company. In the event of the above, the acquiring company or transferee will respect the rights and obligations as described in this Privacy Policy.

The Services are not designated to individuals under the age of 16. If you are under 16 you should not use the Services nor provide any Personal Information to us.

We reserve the right to access and verify any Personal Information which is collected from you by us. In the event that we become aware that an individual under the age of 16 shared any information, we will discard such information. If you have any reason to believe that a minor shared any information with us, please contact us at [privacy@logz.io](mailto:privacy@logz.io).

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time, in our sole discretion, and the most current version will always be posted on our Website (as reflected in the “Last Revised” heading). We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.

Your continued use of the Services, following the posting of such amendments on our Website, constitutes your acknowledgment and consent of such amendments to the Privacy Policy and your agreement to be bound by the terms of such amendments.

If you have any general questions regarding the Services or the information that we collect about you and how we use it, please contact us at [privacy@logz.io](mailto:privacy@logz.io).

##  **Information about us**

 **The details of the Company are as follows:**

Logshero Ltd.  
28 Ha’arba’a St.,  
Tel Aviv, Israel, 6473925

 **The details of the EU Representative are as follows:**

Logz.io UK Limited  
37 Broadhurst Gardens  
London, United Kingdom  
NW6 3QT
